[{"answer": "It is.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "It is an extraordinarily outrageously audacious plot, isn't it?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "It would -- I think it would be pretty difficult for them to deny.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "I mean, given the sums of money involved, given the elaborate nature of the plot, is it conceivable that Mahmoud Ahmadinejad or the Supreme Leader Ayatollah Khamenei, that didn't know about this?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, what we hope happens now is that this is an opportunity for the administration to engage our European allies in tougher sanctions.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "But what does that actually mean in practice?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "OGERS: Well, the good news is when the early stages of this that they were briefed as to the security that they might need to undergo to make sure that if something went wrong in the operation and they were able to get there, that they would be safe and able to keep the ambassador safe as well as other security precautions.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "What would you imagine their reaction may be?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Every day.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Do you ever sit here, just the three of you sometimes, and think, how did we get here?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "You know, I had the occasion to go back to the house I grew up in Ashton, Birmingham a few months ago.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "I mean I just wonder whether sometimes you have that moment where you just think how did this happen?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "If you had your time again, would you choose to be in that MTV show?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, I'm lucky.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "And what do you think of that, coming from Britain and going back there and seeing it's so much more prevalent now, given what it did to you and your life and the impact on your family?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Lucky is not the word.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Do you feel lucky that none of your kids ended up like Amy Winehouse?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "I think she said -- she's including you as one of the children, Ozzy.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "What about you?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "But then at the same time, it has nothing to do with the size, the age, the width, (INAUDIBLE), it's to do with the look.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "And doing this?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "What do you feel?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "I mean, that's an extraordinary moment to reach, isn't it?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "It was -- it was pretty damn scary because, you know, you're in a house, no neighbors each side, your kids are asleep.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Well, in a funny way, in the movie -- in the movie, it was a bit surreal watching that because, Sharon was able to kind of deal with it in a relatively calm way when in fact it must have been at the time just grotesque, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Oh, god, yes.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What was the answer when you ask yourself that?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "No, as harder -- as hard as Ozzy would hit me, I would clobber him back.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "How would you imagine that you're a shrinking violet in any relationship, Sharon?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Honestly, it's just kind of --", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "What do you feel when you hear that?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Never in front of the kids?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "You never hit a girl.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Yes, that's exactly right.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "So what about you (EXPLETIVE DELETED) hitting us then?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "But do you feel, Ozzy, you're a completely different human being now?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "It was great fun until it wasn't.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "And to put the flipside on it, was it for a long time great fun being Ozzy?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Enough of this?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Sharon, would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "And Jack just cracked up.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Had you pissed on me as well?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "You don't agree, Ozzy?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Maybe was.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "It wasn't Jack reacting to you?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Jack, do you remember the incident your mom is talking about?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "What have you got against bats?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I did some have crazy stuff when I was out there, you know.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "My mom's a very strong-willed woman.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Am I misreading the tea leaves?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Without a doubt.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Is that understood?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "The whole thing was --", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Even now, though?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Dad likes to slam things.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Ozzy, would you say you have anger management issues?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "It was the strangest thing because we were all on such a big high from the show being such a success.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "What was that like, do you think, in reality for the family?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Did you think Ozzy could have coped if you had died?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "No one really told me the severity of it.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Jack, what was it like for you?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "I wanted to get out.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "What were you thinking, Ozzy, as you were lying in hospital?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Never boring, is it?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "On his death bed, this is what he -- on his death bed, he said to me -- the only thing I have to say to you -- he thought al drugs were speed or sleeping pills.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "How did he feel about the way you were enjoying all that fame?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "I know he would.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Do you think he would have been very proud of you, of what you've now done?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "I got the most amazing gifts from my father, the gift of music.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "When that happened, what was your real emotion when you realized he was no longer going to be any part of your life?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "It wouldn't surprise me.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "ORGAN: Did you ever imagine your father would become a sort of medical advisory board?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "I haven't got a clue.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "How did it keep going?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "Do you feel like all the torment has been worth it?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "Oh yeah.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Jack?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Jack is a lone voice of sanity.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Where did we find little Jack?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "I'm excited.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "I'm in shock.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Ozzy, how are you feeling about this?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "I think it is fabulous.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Good shock?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "You are not a grandma, right?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "Oh!", "docId": "111011pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "Grandma, sit with the kettle and let's have a cup of tea, shall we?", "qSentId": 700}]